airportparkingreservations.com 2019-07-22

# Airport Parking Reservations.com: Discount Airport Parking Reservations at airports nationwide

Updated 2/12/2014   
**The Postal address for AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. is:**

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc.  
1640 5th Street, Suite 202  
Santa Monica, CA 90401 

Our web site is located at: [https://www.airportparkingreservations.com](https://www.airportparkingreservations.com/)

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by clicking this link: [contact us](https://www.airportparkingreservations.com/help#contact). 

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. knows that you care about how your personal information is collected, stored, shared, and used. We value your trust and will work hard to ensure that any personally identifiable information in our possession is handled carefully and professionally. By visiting AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. you are accepting the Privacy Policy described herein. 

### Simply Stated:

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. will not collect personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail, mailing address and telephone number without your knowledge and permission; and we will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the personal information we collect from you. 

### Information Collection:

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. collects general, non-personally identifiable information each time a customer visits our web site. This information is used to allow us to continually improve the service we offer and make the features on our web site easier to use. 

We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our visitors with our parking vendors, advertisers, travel partners and other third parties. 

When you decide to conduct a transaction with AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc., we will collect personal information about you that you voluntarily share with us. We collect personal information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. This personal information may include your name, e-mail and mailing address, telephone number and credit card information. If you decide to become a registered user of this site, you will provide an e-mail address, and select a password that will be required to gain access to portions of our site. 

Third parties may also use tracking technology to collect information from emails, to use for advertising purposes. You may opt-out of this tracking technology and the Digital Advertising Alliance [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

### Use of Cookies:

A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can later be read back from that browser. This is useful for having the browser remember some specific information. AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. may use cookies to improve your browsing experience with us and to give sales credit to third party marketing companies who promote our services. AirportParkingreservations.com, Inc and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website. Your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our web site so that you can more quickly fill-in your personal information on subsequent visits.  This also helps us improve web site functionality, performance and identify technical issues.  AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc may use cookies to serve 'remarketing' advertisements across the internet on other web sites you visit. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, if you do so we will not be able to recognize you as a repeat customer and some of the features on our web site may not work. 

### Use and Sharing of Information:

We share the following personal information with the parking vendor(s) you have chosen to conduct business with: Your name, travel departure & return dates & times, and survey data if you have chosen to participate in our post-trip customer satisfaction survey. We do not share your email address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information with our parking vendors unless it is necessary to resolve a customer service issue. We contract with other companies to perform various functions necessary to operate our business - for example, to process credit cards. We will share with these other companies only that personal Information they require to fulfill their contractual obligations to us. These companies agree that they will not use or disclose that personal information for any other purpose. 

We may have third party advertisers ("advertisers") on our site. These advertisers may use cookies to track general, non-personally identifiable information about the ads you have seen and types of things that you appear interested in. We do not share any Personal information about you with these advertisers or other third party partners unless you give us permission to do so separate from any permission you provide during the registration process. However, these advertisers may have other sources of information and their own privacy practices. These advertisers may also use combined information about your visits to our site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that you may be interested in. When you visit a site that we advertise on, we may place a cookie on your personal computer. 

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. sends the following transaction related emails: a receipt whenever you conduct a transaction on our web site, a 'customer rewards' email waiving our transaction fee on a future reservation, a second copy of your receipt a few days before your departure, and a quality of service survey invitation when you return from your trip. 

From time to time, AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. may contact you by mail or email to make you aware of special offers, new services and other information we believe to be of interest. And, occasionally we send emails to select customers on behalf of carefully selected businesses. 

We always give you the choice to opt-out from receiving non-transaction related emails. If you do not opt-out from receiving these communications, we will send them to you. If you prefer not to receive non-transaction related email from us, please [unsubscribe here](https://www.airportparkingreservations.com/unsubscribe) and we will remove you from our mail-to list. 

### How your Information is Stored:

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. makes every reasonable effort to keep your personal information safe and secure. We also protect the connection between your computer and our server from eavesdropping through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 256 bits. 

### Links to Other Web Sites:

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. may contain links to external web sites that have privacy policies different from ours. We have no control or responsibility for other web sites and recommend that you read each privacy policy prior to taking advantage of any offers. 

### Merger, Sale or Transfer Of Ownership:

In the event that AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. is merged, disposed of, or sold in part or in full, customer information could be one of the assets that are transferred and your personally identifiable information accessed by successor or purchaser. 

### Children:

AirportParkingReservations.com, Inc. does not offer any services pertinent to children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you may use AirportParkingReservations.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy:

Our privacy policy may be revised at any time. To stay informed about changes to our privacy policy, please check back frequently.
